美国是一片被辐射的不毛之地
America is an irradiated wasteland.
其中伫立着一座城池
Within it lies a city.
周边都是一片荒漠
Outside the boundary walls a desert.
是一片被诅咒的土地
A cursed earth.
墙内是一座被诅咒的城市
Inside the walls a cursed city,
从波士顿绵延到华盛顿
stretching from Boston to Washington, D.C.
一片还未破碎的钢筋泥土建筑
An unbroken concrete landscape.
8亿人口生存于这片建于旧世界的废墟之上的
800 million people living in the ruin of the old world
新世界的巨型建筑里
and the mega structures of the new one.
巨型街区 巨型高速公路
Mega blocks. Mega highways.
这就是一号巨城
Mega City One.
气氛令人战栗 窒息
Convulsing. Choking.
因其自身而分崩离析
Breaking under its own weight.
市民们对街道 枪支 帮派
Citizens in fear of the street.
胆战心惊
The gun. The gang.
混乱中唯一为秩序而战的
Only one thing fighting for order in the chaos,
只有法院的男男女女
the men and women of the Hall of Justice.
陪审团
Juries.
DNA检测
身份通过
Executioners.
行刑者
判官
Judges.
新特警判官
1117号广场处需要警员 代号10-10
Responders needed at a square at 1117. Code 10-10.
休闲活动中心发生枪击事件
Leisure complex. Shots fired.
车辆逃逸 正在追捕 请求空中监测
Out of vehicle, in pursuit. Request aerial surveillance.
监控到三名逃逸罪犯
I have a control drone flagging three perps.
子区域20号 5号天桥处需要警员
Responders needed in Sub-Sector 20, Flyover 5.
指认出三名有多件案底在身的通缉犯
We have a positive ID on three suspects wanted on multiple counts.
请听到的判官回复
Any Judges, please respond.
13区的德莱德回复控制中心 正在追捕车辆
Dredd to Control. In pursuit of vehicle, Sector 13.
驾驶轨迹飘忽 疑犯看来吸食过毒品
Driving erratic. Suspects are under the influence of narcotics.
有判官在追我们
Got a Judge on our tail.
什么?
What?
我说有个判官追着我们!
I said we got a Judge on our tail!
干掉他 不然我们死定了!
Take him out or we're dead fucking meat!
该死!
Fuck!
需要支援吗?
Do you require backup?
不需要
No.
混蛋!
Fucker!
我都打不中他! 你他妈给我开直线!
I can't get him! Straighten the fuck out!
请注意 从空中看不到疑犯车辆了
Be advised. We have lost visual.
该死 他快追上我们了!
Fuck, he's right on us!
老兄 我们完了 死定了!
Man, we're dead. We're fucking dead!
呼叫控制中心 罪犯刚撞死一名无辜行人 我去处决他们
Control. Perps just wiped out an innocent. I'm taking them down.
激活人群控制程序
Bike. Activate crowd control.
已激活 市民们 请保持冷静 远离犯罪现场
Activated. Citizens, be calm. Step back from the crime scene.
干涉办案罪将会被判五年徒刑
Interference carries an automatic five-year sentence in the iso-cubes.
嘿 赶紧滚出去!
Hey, fucking get out of here!
呼叫控制中心 请派医务人员到我的方位来 有几名伤者和尸体需要处理
Control. Paramedics to my GPS. Multiple wounded and bodies for resyck.
收到 德莱德
Copy, Dredd.
所有顾客请远离一楼餐饮区 并等待进一步通知
All shoppers are reminded to avoid the level one food courts until further notice.
- 还有其它点心可供选择...  - 闭嘴
- Alternative refreshments can be found...  - Shut the fuck up.
- 我们谈谈吧  - 有什么好谈的 判官?
- Let's talk.  - Talk about what, Judge?
安然无恙地释放人质
Release the hostage unharmed,
我保证你能在监狱里终生监禁 不能假释
and I guarantee you a sentence of life in an iso-cube without parole.
不能假释? 这就是你开出的条件吗?
Life without parole? That's the deal you're offering?
也要你听话才行
Only if you comply.
你的罪行包括多起谋杀罪以及谋杀判官未遂罪
Your crimes include multiple homicide and the attempted murder of a Judge.
如果你不听话 那么只能死刑
If you do not comply, the sentence is death.
判官 你实在算不上谈判专家
You aren't a very good negotiator, Judge.
知道为什么吗? 因为你手上没筹码!
You know why? You got no fucking leverage!
这样吧 你放我走 不然我就打爆她的脑袋 怎么样?
Here's the deal. You let me walk or I blow her fucking brains out. Okay?
谈判结束
Negotiation's over.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
你没听到我说的话吗? 我会杀了这个贱人的!
Didn't you hear what I said? I'll kill the bitch!
我听到了 热能弹
Yeah, I heard you, hotshot.
什么?
What?
我说"热能弹"
I said "hotshot."
控制中心呼叫德莱德
Control to Dredd. Come in.
- 处决完毕了吗?  - 处决完毕
- Is your pursuit resolved?  - Affirmative.
回法院复命 审判长想见你
Report back to the Hall of Justice. The Chief Judge wants to see you.
谢谢你 判官
Thank you, Judge.
1层饮食区30分钟后重新开放 感谢您的耐心等待
The level one food court will reopen in 30 minutes. Thank you for your patience.
她是卡珊德拉·安德森 21岁
Cassandra Anderson. Twenty-one.
出生于距辐射边界100米的街区
Born in a block 100 meters from the radiation boundary wall.
7岁时双亲死于残留辐射导致的癌症
At age seven, she lost both parents to residual-fallout cancer.
跟所有孤儿一样 她在九岁时接受了判官能力倾向测验
As is usual with orphans, she was given a Judge aptitude test at age nine.
虽然认定她不适合做判官
It classified her as unsuitable,
但因为上层的特殊指令还是安排她去学院学习
but she was entered into the Academy on special instruction.
在学院里 她的成绩从来都不能及格
In the Academy, her record was never better than borderline.
最后的学院成绩比及格线低了百分之三
Her final Academy score put her three percentile points below a pass.
那她还穿着制服干嘛?
So what's she doing in a uniform?
- 新手安德森  - 长官
- Rookie Anderson.  - Sir.
有几个人在观察你?
How many people are observing you?
2个
Two.
站在我身边的人你能感知到什么?
What can you tell me about the person I'm with?
男性 另一名判官
Male. Another Judge.
我能感觉到愤怒 自制 但是...
I can feel anger. And control. But...
还有些别的
there's something else.
竭力控制之后 还有些...
Something behind the control. Something...
- 快要...  - 够了 安德森
- almost...  - Okay, Anderson.
这样就行了
That will do.
她是变种人
She's a mutant.
判官委员会决定观察她的状态 你也要观察
The Judges Council have chosen to overlook her status. So you will, too.
她是我们有史以来遇到过的最强大的灵媒
She's the most powerful psychic we've ever come across by a huge margin.
判官们就快输了城市之战
The Judges are losing the war for the city.
我们相信她能帮我们扭转局面
We believe she could be a major asset.
正如我说的 她的期末成绩就也比及格少了百分之三 也算及格边缘了
As I said, her final score was only three points below a pass. It's marginal.
- 不是边缘 就是不及格  - 这姑娘还有一次机会
- It's not marginal. She failed.  - The girl's getting one more chance.
我想要你带她出去 给她实地作战一天 你来监督
I want you to take her out, give her one day in the field. Supervised.
看看她是否能过关
See if she makes the grade.
成败全靠自己 把她丢到困境中去
Sink or swim. Chuck her in the deep end.
现在到处都是困境
It's all the deep end.
全体人员都必须随身携带证件
Personnel are required to carry identification at all times.
一名待评估的菜鸟判官有可能碰上武装冲突
A rookie Judge on assessment is likely to be involved in armed combat.
有五分之一的新人熬不过第一天
One in five don't survive the first day.
可能会要求你去执行重刑犯的现场行刑
You may be required to carry out on-the-spot executions of convicted felons.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
判决错误算你任务失败
Incorrect sentencing is an automatic fail.
不遵守评估长官的直接命令算你任务失败
Disobeying a direct order from your assessment officer is an automatic fail.
主要武器丢失或被攫取算你任务失败
Losing your primary weapon or having it taken from you is an automatic fail.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
- 准备好了吗 菜鸟?  - 准备好了
- Are you ready, rookie?  - I am.
强制车辆检查...
Mandatory vehicle checks...
你的评估现在开始
Your assessment starts now.
妈妈
Ma.
我们有麻烦了
We got trouble.
他们在我地盘上兜售"厉锤帮"的毒品
They were selling Sternhammer product on my level.
几周前我揍了他们一顿以示警告 我猜大概不管用
I warned them off with a beating a couple of weeks ago. Guess it didn't work.
- 你自己摆平不了这种小事?  - 我能摆平
- You can't deal with it yourself?  - I can deal with it.
问题是你想不想杀鸡儆猴
The question is whether you wanna make an example of them.
扒了他们的皮 从阳台扔出去
Skin them. Toss them over the balcony.
要不要先喂一点"慢摇"?
Hit them with a little Slo-Mo first?
当然了
Sure.
把这吃了 混蛋!
Eat this, fucker!
按住他!
Hold him down!
求你了 求你了
Please. Please.
放了我吧
Please.
桃树区附近需要警员 我们接到三连环凶杀案的报案
Responders in the vicinity of Peach Trees. We have a report of a triple homicide.
医护人员已到现场 用警戒线隔离该区域
The paramedic is on site and is cordoning off the area.
每分钟都会收到12起严重罪行报案
Twelve serious crimes reported every minute.
每天1万7千起
17,000 per day.
- 我们只能回应差不多百分之六  - 哪百分之六?
- We can respond to around 6%.  - Which 6%?
这是你的评估 菜鸟 你来选
Your show, rookie. You tell me.
桃树区 三连环凶杀案
Peach Trees. Multiple homicide.
德莱德呼叫指挥中心 我们去处理桃树区的案子
Dredd to Control. We'll take Peach Trees.
收到
Copy that.
嘿 乔伊 让我们看看你有什么本事吧
Hey, Joey, show us what you've got.
好了 菜鸟 你对桃树区都知道些什么?
Okay, rookie. What do you know about Peach Trees?
长官 桃树区有7万5千名已登记的市民
Sir. Peach Trees houses 75,000 registered citizens.
也是13区中犯罪率最高的地区 失业率达到96%
It has the highest crime rate in Sector 13. Unemployment rate of 96%.
半数以上的住宅区同平民窟一个水准
And more than half the residential levels here are classed as slums.
菜鸟
Rookie.
判决吧
Judgment.
流浪者该判以3周监禁 但要优先处理谋杀案吧?
Vagrancy, three weeks, iso-cubes. But prioritize murders?
判断正确 你最好在我们回来前离开
Correct. Don't be here when we get back.
是的 谢了 判官
Yes. Thanks, Judge.
请待在安全线之外
Please remain behind the security tape.
你为什么想成为判官?
So why do you wanna be a Judge?
长官 我想保护这座城市 为之服务 改变现状
Sir. I want to protect and serve the city. To make a difference.
想改变这种德性的街区?
Make a difference to a block like this?
如果你想要这就是你的了
It's yours if you want it.
在司法部门带走我之前 我就出生于这种街区 也在那长大
I was born and raised in a block like this before the Justice Department took me.
我知道那里有善良的人 有努力生活的美好家庭
I know there are good people inside, good families just trying to get by.
是的 我相信我可以创造不同
Yes, I believe I can make a difference.
佩服你
Admirable.
今天商场将于10点关门 还有大量时间供您购物
The mall will be closing today at 10 o'clock. Plenty of time to make your purchases.
有什么线索?
What have you got?
三具死尸横尸街头
Three stiffs in a somewhat fucked-up condition.
拍到那照片了吗?
Did you get a picture of that?
- 你常驻桃树区吗?  - 25楼的医疗中心
- You based in Peach Trees?  - Med Center, level 25.
- 查过身份了吗?  - 差不多了
- You ID'd them?  - Mostly.
这两人是这个大楼的注册居民
These two are registered to this block.
- 他呢?  - 我得拿他的血样
- And him?  - I'll have to run his blood
去做DNA测试才能知道
through a DNA profiler.
如果我能搞清楚哪些血是他的
If I can figure out which blood is his.
你怎么看 菜鸟?
What do you make of this, rookie?
我不知道 长官
I don't know, sir.
是吃了"慢摇"后的痕迹
It's a cold-burn from a Slo-Mo inhaler.
"慢摇"?
Slo-Mo?
只要吸上小小一口 就能效力持久
Only just hit the grid, but it's making big waves.
使大脑感觉时间的流逝只有平时速度的百分之一
Makes the brain feel as if time is passing at 1% its normal speed.
这些家伙估计以为自己一直在空中
Guess it felt like a long way down.
身份已验证
Positive on your IDs.
资料显示这些人都因私藏毒品定罪 现在传送数据给你
All showing convictions for possession of narcotics. Transmitting data now.
三流罪犯 毒贩子 没有已知的帮派涉嫌 你怎么分析?
Small-time perps. Junkies. No known gang affiliation. What's your analysis?
吸了毒 扒了皮 暴尸街头
Drugged. Skinned. Displayed in public.
我觉得这是惩罚性的杀戮 有人想藉此传递讯息
I think it's a punishment killing. Someone's trying to send a message.
是呀 别惹到妈妈帮
Yeah. Don't fuck with the Ma-Ma clan.
妈妈帮?
Ma-Ma clan?
从她卖淫开始 我们就对她记录在案了
We have her on record from her whoring days.
这照片有点老了
The picture's pretty old,
不过就是她 玛德琳·玛德里盖尔 人称妈妈
but that's her. Madeline Madrigal, aka Ma-Ma.
从第九娱乐区出来的妓女
Ex-hooker from the S-9 pleasure district.
她被一个皮条客阴了之后就不干了 然后自己报了仇
Quit working when she got sliced up by a pimp. She got her own back.
人们都说她用牙齿阉了那个家伙
Block legend says she's feminized the guy with her teeth.
接手了他的事业 再也没走过老路
Took over his business interests and never looked back.
换了别人 你肯定会说胡扯 对吧?
Anyone else, you'd say it was bullshit, right?
但妈妈不一样 她的商标就是暴力
Not with Ma-Ma. Her trademark is violence.
不久前 有三个主要帮派极力争夺桃树区的控制权
Not so long ago, there were three main gangs hustling for control of Peach Trees.
皮约特国王帮 红龙帮和判决派
The Peyote Kings, the Red Dragons, the Judged.
然后妈妈帮来了
Then Ma-Ma arrived.
他妈的怎么回事?
What the fuck?
快跑!
Let's go!
她控制了这栋大楼的顶层 然后开始一路向下
Took over the top floor of the block and started working her way down.
九个月之后 她掌控了一切
Nine months later, she had control of everything.
从1楼到200楼
Levels one to 200
都是她的地盘
are hers.
她怎么逃脱惩罚的?
How did she get away with it?
你知道我们桃树区这多久才能来一个判官吗?
You know how often we get a Judge up in Peach Trees?
现在这不是来了一个嘛
Well, you got one now.
受害者是39层的注册公民
The victims are registered to apartments on level 39.
看起来像地盘问题被杀的 所以罪犯应该就在附近
Likely killed over a turf issue, so perps will be in the vicinity.
菜鸟
Rookie.
查出这个集团在这层的操作中心 然后予以重击
Find out where the clan operate on this level, and hit it hard.
应该就是这了
That would be here.
我觉得这是你第一次实战吧
I take it this is your first time in non-sim combat.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我还在想你什么时候能想起来去拿自己的头盔呢
Been wondering when you'd remember you left your helmet behind.
长官 头盔会干扰我的超感能力
Sir, a helmet can interfere with my psychic abilities.
一枚子弹可能会干扰得更厉害
Think a bullet might interfere with them more.
- 准备好了吗?  - 是的 长官
- Are you ready?  - Yes, sir.
- 你看着不像准备好了  - 肾上腺素不稳而已 长官
- You don't look ready.  - Just adrenaline, sir.
菜鸟
Rookie.
安德森 判决
Anderson. Judgment.
罪行是私藏及使用受管制药物 判2年徒刑
Crime, possession and use of controlled substances. Sentence, two years iso-cubes.
不要跟我说 报告指挥中心去
No, don't tell me. Tell Control.
- 安德森呼叫控制中心  - 收到
- Anderson to Control.  - Copy.
请派两辆救护车到桃树区39楼 我们这有
Requesting meat wagon to Peach Trees, level 39. We have
4具尸体要清理 还有8人要监禁
four bodies for resyck and eight live for the iso-cubes.
收到 救护车随后就来
Copy that. Meat wagon inbound.
好了 拷上他们吧
All right. Let's get them cuffed.
快起来
Move. Up.
长官 这人是帮派成员 他...
Sir, this one's a gang member. He...
长官 就是他
Sir, it's him.
他是谁?
Him who?
就是杀了中庭那些人的凶手
The man who murdered the people in the atrium.
确定吗?
You're sure?
99%确定
99%.
不能因为99%的嫌疑就处决犯人
Can't execute a perp on 99%.
如果你现在坦白的话就省了我很多填表格的功夫
Save me a lot of paperwork if you just confess right now.
我们把他带走吧 看看几个钟头的审讯后他还能嘴硬多久
We'll take him in. See how he holds up after a few hours of interrogation.
该死
Shit.
是判官 不 不会吧 糟了
Judges. No, no, no, no.
凯勒? 39楼出了问题
Caleb? There's a problem on level 39.
判官们找到了那个据点 把那里捣毁了
Judges hit the distribution point and shot the place up.
带走了几个小伙子
Took out a few of the boys.
那又怎么样?
So what? We're overdue a bust.
只是判官们露露脸而已 提醒下市民他们的存在
It's just the Judges showing their faces, reminding the citizens they exist.
- 没这么简单 妈妈 他们抓走了凯  - 处决了吗?
- No, Ma. They picked up Kay.  - Executed?
他们正打算押他回去审讯 他们正带他离开
Interrogation. They're taking him in right now.
该死
Fuck.
- 如果凯招了...  - 如果他们用刑的话 他肯定会招供
- If Kay talks...  - If they're taking him in, he'll talk.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
这人还有气
That one's still breathing.
已经占领控制室了
Control room is secure.
路由器装好了 你可以开始了
Router's in. You're good to go.
区域控制中心
Sector Control.
区域控制中心 这里是桃树区控制中心
Sector Control, this is Peach Trees Control,
你们是否收到我们今天战争防御系统测试的通知
I just wanna check you were notified about the def-con systems test today.
收到 桃树区 我们没有战争防御系统测试
Copy that. Peach Trees, we don't have you down for a def-con test.
- 不 肯定有 如果你查查...  - 这里什么都没查到
- Yeah, we must be. If you check the...  - I've got nothing.
去死吧 混蛋区域中心!
God fucking damn it, Sector!
我今天都他妈通知三次了!
I put in the notification myself three fucking times!
我们现在就要开始测试了!
We are good to go right now!
我的上司现在就在我旁边
I've got my supervisor breathing down my neck.
别冲动 桃树区 我来处理一下
Hold fire, Peach Trees. Let me get on this.
好了 我把你放上系统了
Okay. I put you on the system.
通知了法院和所有紧急服务都忽略你的状态
Hall of Justice and all emergency services are notified to ignore your status.
你可以随时开始测试了
You can run the test any time you like.
非常感谢 区域中心 你救了我的命
Appreciate that, Sector. You just saved my ass over here.
不用客气 桃树区
You're welcome, Peach Trees.
长官 他在思考怎么夺走你的枪
Sir, he's thinking about making a move for your gun.
嗯
Yeah.
他又改主意了
He just changed his mind.
好
Yeah.
下一层 中庭
输入密码你就可以登录了
Then enter the pass key and you should be inside.
进入安全系统
Security protocols accessed.
进入战斗防御系统
War protocol accessed.
打开防爆屏蔽
Blast shield initiated.
警告过你了 站起来 跟我们走
Warned you. Get up. You're headed for the cubes.
请离开门口
Stand clear of doors.
所有市民请保持冷静
All residents remain calm.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
封锁完毕
Lockdown complete.
你可以说话了
You're patched in.
桃树区的居民听好了
Peach Trees.
我是妈妈
This is Ma-Ma.
这栋大楼里的某处有两个判官
Somewhere in this block are two Judges.
我想要他们死
I want them dead.
在我得到我想要的东西之前 这栋大楼会一直封锁
Until I get what I want, the block is locked down.
所有楼层的帮派成员都去搜寻判官
All clan, every level, hunt the Judges down.
其他人乖乖把走廊让出来
Everyone else, clear the corridors
枪击结束前都别他妈挡着我们的路
and stay the fuck out of our way until the shooting stops.
如果我听说有人帮了判官
If I hear of anyone helping the Judges,
我会杀了他们 还有他们的孩子
I will kill them and the next generation of their family.
至于判官...
As for the Judges...
我们最好快走
We better move.
稳坐不动是逃跑
Sit tight, or run.
都毫无区别 你们死定了
Makes no difference. You're mine.
控制中心 我们在桃树区碰到状况了 收到没?
Control, we have a situation developing in Peach Trees. Do you copy?
- 控制中心 收到了吗?  - 我的无线电也断了
- Control, do you copy?  - My comms are down, too.
屏蔽器肯定干扰了我们的无线电传输
Shielding must be blocking our transmissions.
我们要去医疗中心
We'll head for the Med Center.
他们在这里!
They're here!
- 下令吧  - 长官?
- Call it.  - Sir?
你还在评估中 菜鸟 快下令
You're on assessment, rookie. Call it.
现场有多名武装分子 视线受阻 要用烟雾弹
Multiple armed targets. Obstructed line of sight. Gas grenades.
戴上呼吸器
Respirators.
建议你屏住呼吸
Advise you hold your breath.
我要你们完全控制北边和东边的走廊
I want the north and east corridor totally covered.
萨尔负责控制西边和南边 拿出你们的武器吧
Sal's got the west and the south. And spread out your hardware.
我们要把这些判官带回去给妈妈
We're gonna hand these Judges back to Ma-Ma on a plate.
- 他妈的 专心点  - 判官们要来了!
- Stay fucking focused.  - Judges got it coming!
- 判官 来抓我啊  - 我们得摆平他们
- Judge, come and get me.  - We're gonna have to go through them.
闪光弹
Stun grenade.
- 杀了那个混蛋  - 给他们来点好消息吧
- Kill that motherfucker.  - Let's give them the good news.
- 到走廊上面去 兄弟们  - 搞死那些判官
- Man up that corridor, man.  - Fuck up the Judges.
干掉他们
Fuck them.
桃树区的居民们 我是执法人员
Citizens of Peach Trees. This is the law.
你觉得你算什么东西?
Who do you think you are coming up in here?
立刻退下 否则我们会使用致命武器扫荡这片区域
Disperse immediately, or we will use lethal force to clear the area.
- 声音从哪发出来的?  - 那边 入口处走廊
- Where's that coming from?  - Over there. Access corridor.
警告过你们了
You have been warned.
给你们20秒时间投降
You now have 20 seconds to comply.
是你们该投降才对吧 判官 我们有10个人 你们只有2个
It's you doing the complying, Judge. There's 10 of us, only two of you.
你们还是从门那边出来吧
Why don't you step out from behind that doorway,
否则我们会把你们都轰出来
or we're gonna blow the fuck out of you.
还有十秒钟
Ten seconds to comply.
- 去死吧 判官  - 给你五秒
- Fuck you, Judge.  - You got five.
多谢提醒
Thanks for the heads-up.
求求你们
Please.
你还在等什么 菜鸟?
What are you waiting for, rookie?
他的罪行是谋杀判官未遂 该判死刑
His crime is attempted murder of a Judge. His sentence is death.
明白 长官
Yes, sir.
开门
Open up.
- 快打开!  - 不行 判官
- Open up!  - Negative, Judge.
你知道发生了什么事
You know what's going on out here.
我们要找个能防御的地方
We need a place we can defend.
那你们最好找别的地方吧 这里是医疗实施 属于中立区
Then you better find someplace else. This is a medical facility. Neutral ground.
中立? 你并不中立 你在选择立场
Neutral? You're not neutral. You're choosing sides.
桃树区被沉重的大门封闭了 这些门旨在抵挡袭击
Peach Trees has been sealed by blast doors designed to withstand attack.
没人出得去 也没人进得来
No one's getting out. No one's coming in.
这栋大楼里所有的帮派成员都在追杀你们
And you have every clan affiliate in the block after your blood.
根本不用选立场 你们死定了
There are no sides. You're already dead.
看起来今天医疗中心关门早了
Looks like the Med Center's closed early today.
把武器调到消音模式 最好的办法就是隐秘点
Switch weapon to silencer mode. Our best bet now is to go covert.
保存好弹药 不到万不得已不要开枪
Conserve ammunition. And don't shoot unless you're gonna hit.
- 长官 犯人怎么办?  - 解释一下
- Sir, what about the prisoner?  - Explain.
这种情况下 他是种负担
Under the circumstances, he could be a liability.
也是三连环凶杀案的主要嫌疑人
Also a prime suspect in three homicides.
你怎么看 菜鸟? 想放了他吗?
What do you say, rookie? Wanna cut him loose?
不想 长官
No, sir.
起来!
Get up!
走吧 走 快点!
Go, go, go, go!
等等
Hold up.
- 快走!  - 小心点
- Move!  - Keep your eyes peeled.
老兄 别再他妈的对我指手画脚了!
Man, stop telling me what to fucking do!
我知道这玩意...
I know that new shit...
凯西?
Cathy?
- 是谁呀?  - 凯西 开门
- Who's there?  - Cathy, open the door.
我们不会伤害你的
We're not gonna hurt you.
安全了
Clear.
把这女人关到不能发警报的地方
Secure the woman somewhere she can't raise any alarms.
不行
We can't.
她有个孩子 睡在隔壁房间
She has a baby. Asleep in the next room.
如果不知道她什么时候能被解救 就不能把她关起来
We can't secure her if we don't know when she'll be freed.
孩子的父亲呢?
Is there a father?
出去找我们了
He's out there. Looking for us.
说吧 把你刚才想的话说出来
Say that. What you were just thinking.
- 你怎么会...  - 没事的 说吧
- How did you...  - It's okay. Go ahead.
我不会发警报的
I'm not raising any alarms.
如果外面的人不知道你们在哪 你们就不会杀他们了
If the men out there don't know where you are, you won't be killing them.
继续说
Go on.
这附近有部货梯
There's a service elevator near here.
标志上说已经坏了
The sign says it's broken, but
但只要按的是75楼以上的按钮还是能用的
it works as long as you're hitting a button above level 75.
我只是想让你们离开我的楼层 离开我的家人
I just want you off my level. Away from my family.
- 凯西 我...  - 不用谢我
- Cathy, I...  - Don't thank me.
不是为了你 我只是不想再见到你了
It's not for you. I just don't wanna see you again.
你不会见到了
You won't.
这种毒品的性能是我从没见过的
This drug shifts like nothing I've ever seen.
如果我们成功了就能控制整个城市了
If we play this right, we could take the whole fucking city.
唯一的危险就是我们会扩张得太快
The only danger is we expand too fast.
之前几天里 我们在三个新街区增加了据点
In the last few days, we've added distribution to three new blocks.
很快 我们就考虑侵入9区和15区
And pretty soon, we're looking at making inroads into Sectors 9 and 15.
15区依旧是红龙帮的地盘
Fifteen is still Red territory.
妈妈
Ma.
你最好快点过来
You better come quick.
看 这里死了一个 也许医疗中心外面还有11个
Okay. We got one here, maybe 11 outside the Med Center.
楼梯井有8个 18楼还有5个人
There's eight in the stairwell and another five on level 18.
他们都放倒了30多个人 自己却毫发无伤
They've downed 30 plus and haven't even taken a scratch.
他们现在在哪?
Where are they now?
不知道 不过他们似乎往楼上来了
I don't know, but they seem to be moving their way up the block.
不 等等 我找到了 他们在76楼西侧
No, wait, wait. I just picked them up. They're on level 76, west quadrant.
还要做公共广播吗?
Do you want me to patch you back into the PA?
我们可以让60到80楼的人去夹击他们
We could get level 60 through 80 converging on them.
不 你能把他们封在那里吗?
No. Can you seal them in there?
当然能 战争防御系统让我能安全控制这栋大楼
Sure. War override gives me total control of the building.
这可不妙
That's not good.
完全封锁 他们无路可逃了
Full lockdown. They're going nowhere.
我想干干净净处理这事 他们不领情 那我们就大干一场吧
I tried to do this clean, but they wouldn't let me. So now we do it messy.
太迟了 判官
Too late, Judge.
凯勒 会话
Caleb, come in.
妈妈
Ma.
我们把判官困住了 现在可以干掉他们了
We've got them cornered. We're taking them down right now.
我们需要氧乙炔才能隔断铁栅栏
We'd need oxyacetylene to cut through.
他们知道我们的位置 为什么不来追杀我们?
They know where we are. Why aren't they coming after us?
我也在奇怪这一点
That's what worries me.
把他带回主厅去 坚守住电梯井
Take him back to the main lobby. Hold position behind the elevator shaft.
把它作为防守阵地
Be a good place to defend.
你要去哪?
Where are you going?
如果我没回来 而你又被围攻了
If I don't come back, and you get cornered,
你最好别被活捉
you might not wanna get taken alive.
你自己决定
Your call.
长官
Sir.
离门远点!
Get away from the door!
坐下来!
Sit down!
他说得没错
He's right, you know.
就是你最好别被活捉这事
About not wanting to be taken alive.
帮派成员会对你这种姑娘能做的事...
The stuff the clan would do to a girl like you...
很下流
nasty.
我们以前抓过一个女孩 跟你差不多大 然后...
We had a girl one time, girl about your age and...
不管怎么说...
Well, anyway...
我只是想说 把最后一发子弹留给你自己吧
I'm just saying, save the last bullet for yourself.
好呀 我也会把倒数第二发留给你
Yeah, and I'll save the second to last one for you.
当然可以
Sure.
你是变种人吧?
So you're a mutant?
你们这种可怜人要不三头六臂 要不缺胳膊少腿的
Most of you poor fuckers got three stumpy arms, or no arms.
我觉得你走大运了 全身部件都齐全得很
But I guess you lucked out. You fit together pretty well.
灵媒啊 太失败了
Psychic. So fucked up.
我听说过你们这种人
Yeah, I heard about your kind.
很难相信这是真的
Kind of hard to believe it's real.
比如你能感知我现在在想什么吗?
Like what am I thinking about right now?
你正在想象我俩之间的暴力性行为
You're picturing a violent sexual liaison between the two of us
试图吓到我
in a pointless attempt to shock me.
你很厉害 不过我并不是想吓你
You're good. But I wasn't trying to shock you.
如果我想吓你的话 我应该这么想
If I was trying to shock you, I'd have been thinking about this.
你现在在想什么呢?
What are you thinking about now, huh?
- 他妈的怎么回事?  - 快进来
- What the fuck was that?  - Get back inside.
都他妈快点
Hurry the fuck up.
赶紧挪一挪
Move your fucking asses.
走! 快走!
Move! Move!
回屋子里去 快进屋子!
Back in the house. Get in the house, now!
该死!
Shit!
开火!
Fire!
弗兰克! 弗兰克! 快跑!
Frank! Frankie! Let's go!
让我来
Move.
后退!
Get back!
集中火力
Concentrate the fire.
大威力爆炸弹!
High ex!
快走!
Move!
他们不可能还活着
There's no way they survived.
活要见人 死要见尸
They're not dead till we find them dead.
或者尸体一部分也行
Or part of them anyway.
又有信号了
Comms are back on.
控制中心 收到吗?
Control. Do you copy?
收到
Affirmative.
代号10-24 请求立刻派人到我的位置支援
10-24 on my GPS. Request immediate assistance.
收到 10-24 判官遭到攻击
Copy, 10-24. Judges under fire.
显示你的位置在13区的桃树区 请确认
Showing your location as Peach Trees, Sector 13. Confirm.
确认 请注意 建筑的防爆大门已开启
Confirm. Be advised, blast door defenses have been triggered.
你能在原地等救援吗?
Can you hold your current GPS?
不行
Negative.
如果他们来抓我们 我们就无路可逃了
If they come for us, we've got nowhere to go.
收到 后援已出发 请务必活着
Copy that. Backup is on its way. Just stay alive.
我们得进去
We gotta go back in.
该死的 老兄! 怎么回事?
God damn it, man! What the fuck?
不! 别 别!
No! No, no!
你们帮派封锁了整栋大楼
Your gang locks down a whole block.
大肆屠杀住在那半个层面的男女老少
Massacres an entire quadrant of men, women and children,
就为了杀两个判官
just to take out two Judges.
你觉得算是滥杀无辜了吗?
Sound like overkill to you?
我来告诉你我的想法
I'll tell you what I think.
我觉得要是一开始就处决了你 妈妈就会让我们离开这
I think if we'd executed you at the bust, Ma-Ma would have let us walk out of here.
她只是不想让你被带回区法院
What she doesn't want is you taken back to the Sector house.
她不想让你被审问 害怕你会招供些什么
She doesn't want you interrogated. She's afraid of what you might say.
这就让我很好奇
And that's got me curious.
- 快说!  - 去死吧!
- Spill it!  - Fuck you!
长官
Sir.
长官!
Sir!
如果你让我来 他没必要开口
If you leave it to me, he doesn't have to speak.
你想干什么呢 贱人?
What are you up to, bitch?
欢迎来到你大脑里的世界
Welcome to the inside of your head.
这里还真是空空如也
It's kind of empty in here.
我不知道这又是什么超能力 不过如果我的手没被铐住的话...
I don't know what kind of mutant shit this is, but if my hands weren't cuffed...
如果你不愿意 你就不会被铐住
You aren't cuffed, if you don't wanna be.
既然在我的大脑里 那想做什么都行吗?
My head. Do what I like?
当然了
Sure.
你想着要伤害我并不能真的伤到我
Thinking about hurting me doesn't actually hurt me.
是呀 你赢了
Yeah. Points to you.
不过还有一个方法
Except there is that thing.
什么方法?
What thing was that?
我知道怎么吓死你
That I know how to freak you the fuck out.
看吧 如果你说现在是我的脑子
See, if you're talking about my fucked-up head
和你的脑子对抗
versus your fucked-up head,
你的笨蛋大脑肯定得输
your fucked-up head is gonna lose.
我觉得这样才能让你闭嘴
I figured that would shut you up.
嘿 我也会玩思维游戏
Hey. I can play mind games, too.
你这个小贱人! 你这个变态小贱人!
You fucking bitch! You sick fucking bitch!
我们还没开始呢
We haven't even started.
明白了
Got it.
桃树区是一号巨城里所有"慢摇"毒品的生产基地
Peach Trees is the manufacturing base for all the Slo-Mo in Mega City One.
妈妈控制了整个城市里"慢摇"的生产和销售
Ma-Ma's controlling the production and distribution across the whole city.
真有趣
Interesting.
这里是桃树区 有什么可以帮你的吗?
Peach Trees. Can I help you?
我们接到判官保安 称在这里遭到袭击
We're responding to a report of Judges under fire from within this block.
判官遭到袭击? 我都不知道有这种事
Judges under fire? I'm unaware of any such activity.
实际上我们正在进行一场安排好的战争防御测试
We're actually undergoing a scheduled war defense test.
测试停止 立刻打开大门
Not anymore, you're not. Open the blast door right now.
是的 长官 问题是现在软件故障
Yes, sir. The problem is we've had a software malfunction
我无法控制系统了
and I've lost control of the system.
我们这76楼着火了
We've had a fire on level 76.
你最好赶紧弄好系统 否则我就判你妨碍司法执行罪
You better get control fast. Or I'm slapping you with an obstruction of justice charge.
要关在监狱里5年
Five years in the cubes, mandatory.
好的 长官 马上就处理 谢了
Will do, sir. I'm on it right now. Thank you.
我们有了妈妈的新罪证
We have new intel about Ma-Ma,
也让控制中心增派支援了
and we've managed to get a 10-24 to Control.
参数在变 我们现在能怎么干 安德森?
Parameters are shifting. What are the options, Anderson?
保持移动状态 躲避敌人进一步侦查 或者找地方防卫
Keep moving and attempt to avoid further detection, or find a place to defend.
跟之前一样 除了我们现在知道后援快来了
Same as before, except now we know backup's inbound.
你给了我们两个选择 抵抗或者躲藏
You're giving us two options. Defend or hide.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
我们攻击怎么样? 直捣黄龙去抓妈妈
What about we attack? Head straight for Ma-Ma.
这也算选项吗?
Is that an option?
是呀 她有罪 我们是判官
Well, she's guilty. We're Judges.
长官 有后援在路上 我觉得我们应该按兵不动 直到情势对我方有利
Sir, with backup inbound, I think we should wait until the odds have shifted in our favor.
回答错了?
Wrong answer?
你是灵媒 该知道的
You're the psychic.
安全
Clear.
为什么不开枪打他?
Why didn't you shoot him?
什么意思 为什么我不打他? 你为什么不开枪?
What do you mean, why didn't I shoot him? Why didn't you?
- 好吧 我们可以现在动手  - 动手吧
- Okay, we could do it now.  - Do it.
- 不 你来  - 你来!
- No, you do it.  - You do it!
该死! 该死!
Shit! Shit!
为什么要让我们找到?
Why did it have to be us who found him?
好了 来吧 来吧
All right. Come on. Come on.
信息终端 我们来查查地图
Info terminal. Let's check the schematics.
不许动!
Freeze!
为什么?
Why?
什么为什么?
Why what?
为什么我不能动?
Well, why should I freeze?
因为你一动我就会开枪
Because otherwise I'll shoot you.
枪的保险不开就开枪?
With the safety on?
开了
It isn't.
你们想要什么 孩子们? 运尸袋还是蹲监狱?
How do you want it, kids? Body bags or juve-cubes?
对我来说没差别
Makes no difference to me.
该死!
Fuck!
电击弹!
Stun!
你死定了
You are so fucked.
- 金发妞  - 快点!
- Blondie.  - Come on!
来吧 贱人
Come on, you bitch.
按住那个贱人
Hold that bitch down.
天啊
Jesus.
- 现在 我该怎么处理你?  - 你什么都不用做
- Now then, what am I gonna do with you?  - You're going to do nothing.
都是你闯的大祸
All this trouble is your doing.
你被发现后 要么就该杀了判官 要么就自杀
When you got busted, you should have killed the Judges or been killed yourself.
但是你却像个傻瓜一样被带走了
But instead you let yourself get taken like the dumb fuck you are.
可是我...
But I...
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
我该亲手杀了你 但今天我已经损失太多 不能再损兵折将了
I'd kill you myself, but I already lost plenty today. I can't afford to lose more.
迟早司法部门的人都会冲进这防爆大门
Sooner or later, the Justice Department is gonna come through the blast doors
来找他们的判官
looking for their Judges.
他们只会找到尸体 一个死在25楼
They'll find their bodies all shot up. One on level 25,
一个死在"慢摇"的工厂里 他们缉毒任务失败了
one in the Slo-Mo den. Just a bust that went wrong.
也就是说不能折磨她
That means no torture.
不能强奸 不能扒皮 只能往脑袋和胸口开上几枪
No raping, no skinning. Just a bunch of bullets to the head and chest.
- 听明白了吗?  - 明白了
- Do you understand me?  - Yes.
- 真他妈明白了吗?  - 是的
- Do you fucking understand me?  - Yes.
妈妈
Ma.
他回来了
He's back.
另一个判官 他把自己接入了一个终端
It's the other Judge. He's patched himself into one of the terminals.
- 我觉得他是想进入广播系统  - 你不能阻止他吗?
- I think he's trying to access the PA.  - Can't you stop him?
我能关闭整个系统
I can shut down the whole system,
但如果你让他说话 我就能查出他用的是哪个终端
but if you let him talk, I can trace which terminal he's using.
我们就能知道他到底在哪了
We'll know exactly where he is.
桃树区的居民们
Inhabitants of Peach Trees.
我是判官德莱德
This is Judge Dredd.
让他说
Let him talk.
我只想提醒一下你们
In case you people have forgotten,
这栋大楼是和这座城市其他部分一样 受同样的法律管制
this block operates under the same rules as the rest of the city.
妈妈不是法律
Ma-Ma is not the law.
我才是法律
I am the law.
妈妈只是个普通的罪犯
Ma-Ma is a common criminal.
犯了谋杀罪
Guilty of murder.
还有生产及销售"慢摇"毒品的罪行
Guilty of the manufacture and distribution of the narcotic known as Slo-Mo.
现在 她被判了死刑
And as of now, under sentence of death.
任何妨碍我执法的人
Any who obstruct me in carrying out my duty
都会被当作她的从犯而处决
will be treated as an accessory to her crimes.
我已经警告了你们
You have been warned.
至于你 妈妈...
And as for you, Ma-Ma...
审判时间到
Judgment time.
查到了 他就我们下面10楼的地方 南边阳台 5号终端
I got him. He's only 10 levels below us. South quad balcony. Terminal 5.
混球
Motherfucker.
混蛋怎么还没倒下
Fucker still hasn't gone down.
不是他
It's not him.
燃烧弹
Incendiary.
我们怎么才能抓住这个家伙?
How the fuck are we gonna stop this guy?
报警
Call 911.
有判官从这栋大楼里发了支援请求
Got a 10-24 from this block.
2名判官遭到攻击 要求紧急支援 而你们却站在外面
Two Judges under fire, requesting urgent assistance and you're standing outside.
大楼封锁了 他们的防御系统出了故障
Block's under lockdown. Malfunction with their defense system.
立刻打开大门!
Open up. Now!
你们可以走了
You're relieved.
出了什么事?
So what have we got?
2名判官触发了地盘争斗 判官为履行职责不幸身亡
Two Judges trigger a turf war. Judges die in pursuit of duty.
- 杀了判官的那些犯人呢?  - 就躺在这呢
- And the perps who killed the Judges?  - Laid out here.
- 看来的确如此  - 抱歉
- Sounds right.  - Excuse me.
这不是事实 我从头到尾都在这里
It's not what's happened. I've been here from the start.
这些杀戮都是一个帮派干的 就是妈妈帮
This killing's all about one gang. The Ma-Ma clan.
从枪声判断
And from the sound of gunfire,
至少有1名判官还活着
I'd say at least one of your two Judges is still alive.
- 你会出庭作证吗?  - 当然了
- Are you prepared to testify to that?  - Sure.
100万
One million credits.
100万?
A million?
你惹到了一个判官 你知道他是谁吗?
You have a problem with a Judge. You know who he is?
不知道
No.
我知道 100万
I do. One million.
好吧
Fine.
卡普兰 你负责保护客户安全 陈和阿法拉兹 跟我去把他找出来
Kaplan, protection detail on client. Chan, Alvarez, we're flushing him out.
明白
You got it.
- 另一个判官呢? 就是那个菜鸟  - 我们抓了她
- Where's the other one? The rookie.  - We got her here.
- 活着还是死了?  - 活着
- Dead or alive?  - Alive.
弄死她
Make her dead.
弹药量不足
你 说出你的身份
You, there. Identify yourself.
- 9区的陈  - 13区的德莱德
- Chan. Sector 9.  - Dredd. Sector 13.
是来支援你的
Responding to your 10-24.
很高兴见到你 德莱德
Good to see you, Dredd.
我也是 你一个人吗?
Likewise. You alone?
不是 来了三人小队 正在往我们这儿靠近
Negative. Three-man squad. Closing on my vector right now.
放轻松
So relax.
装甲队也来了
Cavalry's here.
2个人
Two.
2个?
Two?
有2个人请求了支援
Two of us called in the 10-24.
我很好奇你为什么不问另一个的情况
Wondering why you didn't ask about the other one.
莱克斯 行动!
Lex, move it!
咽气吧 德莱德
Choke on it, Dredd.
你才乖乖咽气吧
Choke on that.
该死!
Shit!
打赌你以为你会让自己的家人为你骄傲 对吧?
Bet you thought you were gonna make your family proud, huh?
现在看来不可能了
Not much chance of that now.
现在 我总是想要一把这枪 这真是...
Now this, I always wanted one of these. This is...
你跑到妈妈帮的地头上就太不走运了 不过不要灰心丧气
You were shit out of luck when you ran into the Ma-Ma clan. But don't feel too bad.
我一生见了许多判官 你不适合做这行
I seen a lot of Judges in my time, and you're just not cut out for this.
我是说 就算你今天没被杀死 明天也会
I mean, if you didn't get killed today, it was gonna be tomorrow.
要不然就是后天
Or it was gonna be the day after that.
不管怎么说
Anyway,
你今天就要死了
today it is.
你还有遗言吗 贱人?
You got any last words, bitch?
真搞笑
That's funny.
我也正准备问你这个问题
I was gonna ask you that.
贱人
Bitch.
身份验证失败
凯死了
Kay's dead.
- 找个地方藏起来  - 你要去哪里?
- Find somewhere to hide.  - Where are you going?
我去摆平那女孩 我先看到她 就开枪
I've got the girl cold. I see her first, I shoot her.
她先看到我 她犹豫了 我还是会开枪
She sees me first, she hesitates, then I shoot her.
现在一个判官值多少钱?
What's the price of a Judge these days?
一百万
Million.
四个人分
Split four ways.
现在只有三个人
Three ways now.
听着不错
Suits me.
可没那么好
Doesn't sound like much.
你们背叛了法律
To betray the law.
也背叛了这座城市
Betray the city.
留着这种鬼话去跟菜鸟说吧
Save that shit for the rookies.
我在这街上生活了20年
Twenty years I've been on the streets.
你知道一号巨城是什么吗 德莱德?
You know what Mega City One is, Dredd?
就是个该死的绞肉机
It's a fucking meat grinder.
人们从一头进去
People go in one end.
绞肉就从另一头出来
And meat comes out the other.
我们要做的
All we do
就是转动把手
is turn the handle.
机关枪
Rapid fire.
无弹药
燃烧弹 穿甲弹
Incendiary. Armor piercing.
大威力爆炸弹
High ex.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
只剩两个人了
Two-way split.
如果你不是没子弹了 我都快吓出汗了啦
Yeah, I'd be breaking a sweat, if you hadn't just run out of bullets.
放下你的枪 菜鸟 我是你的后援
Lower your gun, rookie. I'm your backup.
穿甲弹
Armor piercing.
等等
Wait.
等等?
Wait?
你在开玩笑吧? 你竟然说"等等"?
Are you kidding me? Did you just say "wait"?
德莱德判官
Judge Dredd,
伟大的德莱德判官
the Judge Dredd
被枪指着头的时候
finally gets on the wrong end of a gun,
竟然说了句"等等"
and what he says is "wait."
你知道吗? 我以为你会更厉害
You know what? I expected more of you.
我识货 你要我等什么? 等我改变主意吗?
I mean, wait for what? Wait for me to change my mind?
还是你太懦弱了无法坚持看到自己寿终
Wait for another two or three seconds of life
所以想再多苟延残喘两三秒呢?
because you're so fucking weak you just can't stand to see it end?
不
No.
等她开枪打死你
Wait for her to shoot you.
好了
Okay.
基础医疗包
Basic field dressing.
重新装弹药
Reload.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
是的
Yeah.
看起来就准备好了
You look ready.
不 别开枪! 别杀我!
No, don't shoot! Please don't shoot me!
我没武器 我没武器 我能帮你们
I'm not armed. I'm not armed. I can help you.
怎么帮?
How?
妈妈在私人密室里 不过那门是10英寸的钢板
Ma-Ma's in her private quarters, but it's behind 10 inches of steel.
没有密码是根本进不去的 我可以给你们密码
So you can't get in there without the keypad combination. I can give that to you.
我不需要你合作 就能拿到密码
I don't need your cooperation to get the combination from you.
抱歉 对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
走吧
Go.
离开这
Get out of here.
不介意解释一下吧 菜鸟?
Mind explaining yourself, rookie?
放跑一个重罪犯不只是评估失败 更是犯罪
Abetting a felon is not just a fail offense. It's a crime.
我弄丢主要武器的时候 就已经评估失败了
I already picked up the fail when I lost my primary weapon.
我没法成为一名判官 我不用读心术也知道结果
I'm not gonna be a Judge, and I don't need to be a mind-reader to know it.
他是个受害者 不是犯人
He's a victim, not a perp.
在我的评估彻底结束之前 我仍然有豁免别人的权利
And until my assessment is formally over, I'm still entitled to dispense justice.
所以我刚才就放走了他
And that's what I just did by letting him go.
也许那是我唯一能做出的改变吧
Maybe that'll be the one difference I do make.
通往妈妈密室的密码是4-9-4-3-6
The code to Ma-Ma's chambers is 4-9-4-3-6.
结束这一切吧
Let's finish this.
你真是个难缠的人 德莱德
You're a piece of work, Dredd.
可惜我也是
But then so am I.
你以为我不知道总有一天会有这下场吗 要死也得让这块地方陪葬
You think I didn't know I'd get busted some day. Goes with the territory.
这一整层都装满了烈性炸药
This entire level is rigged with enough high explosives
能炸毁最上面50层
to take out the top 50 stories.
要是它们毁了 其它楼层也都完蛋了
If they go, the rest go, too.
很像首饰吧?
Like the jewelry?
这个发信器和我的心跳同步
It's a transmitter synched to my heart beat.
一旦我的心脏停止跳动
My heart stops beating,
这栋楼也爆炸了 所有人都会变成灰烬
the building blows. Everyone in it, ash.
你逃不掉的 判官
You got no way out, Judge.
把枪放下
Put your gun down.
你知道这栋大楼有多少人住着吗?
Do you know how many people live in this block?
这不是谈判 你被判以死刑
This isn't a negotiation. The sentence is death.
你冒不起这个险
You can't afford to take the risk.
我们离地面一千米
We're a kilometer above ground.
你觉得那玩意的发信范围有多广?
What do you figure the range is on that thing?
能穿过100层混凝土吗?
Could it get through 100 levels of concrete?
那200层呢?
How about 200?
我们试试看吧
Let's find out.
妈妈 你犯有多重杀人罪
Citizen Ma-Ma. Your crimes are multiple homicide
生产及销售毒品罪
and the manufacture and distribution of narcotics.
你要为自己辩护吗?
How do you plead?
已记录辩护内容
Defense noted.
好了!
Yeah!
安德森
Anderson.
先处理受害者 就让那些犯人躺在那里吧?
Victims first. Let the perps lay where they lie, huh?
你的评估结束了
Your assessment's now over.
长官
Sir.
我听说你向控制中心申请了支援 我就觉得最好来查看一下
When I heard you'd called in a 10-24, I thought I'd better check it out.
看来我给你的新人成了累赘
Seeing as I forced the rookie on you.
- 里面是怎么回事?  - 缉毒
- So, what happened in there?  - Drug bust.
- 看来你受了不少罪  - 犯人不太合作
- Look like you been through it.  - Perps were uncooperative.
她干得怎么样?
So how did she do?
及格还是不及格?
She a pass or a fail?
上车帮你检查一下 好吧?
Let's take a look, huh?
及格了
She's a pass.
我就知道她会及格的
I knew she would be.
没时间浪费了 走吧
No time to waste. Let's move.
告诉他们到后边去...
Tell them to go to the back...
这就是一号巨城
Mega City One.
8亿人口生存于这片建于旧世界的废墟之上的
800 million people living in the ruin of the old world
新世界的巨型建筑里
and the mega structures of the new one.
混乱中唯一为秩序而战的
Only one thing fighting for order in the chaos,
只有判官
judges.